ezwingame.com 2011-05-20

# Win Free, Win Big, Free Prizes, Free Giveaway Contests - EZWinGame

**EZ WIN GAME**

_[**WWW.EZWINGAME.COM**](http://www.ezwingame.com/)_

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Updated February 11, 2010**

We are committed to keeping your personal information private. Please review our Terms and Conditions (“T&Cs”), any other rules, which also govern your visit and use of our website(s), including but not limited to any Sweepstakes or Game Rules. 

Please read the following general website Privacy Policy carefully before accessing the www.ezwingame.com website (the “Site”), uploading any content or comments or entering any service, audition, competition, or promotion at the Site, so that you are aware of your legal rights and obligations with respect to the Site or EZWin Game LLC and its sponsors, advertisers, affiliates, parents and subsidiaries (individually and collectively, "we," "us," “our,” or "EZWin"). 

Ezwingame has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with  
<http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html>

including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:

EZWin Game LLC

6400 N. Andrews Avenue, Suite #320

Ft. Lauderdale, FL 33309

info@ezwingame.com

If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact   
<http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint>

Visitor access to this Site and the Services (as defined below) is void and unauthorized where prohibited by applicable law or regulation.

**BY USING THIS SITE OR USING OUR SERVICES, INCLUDING PARTICIPATING IN ANY SWEEPSTAKES OR GAMES ON OUR SITE,  
YOU (I) SIGNIFY YOUR IRREVOCABLE ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY; AND (II) REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE OF LEGAL AGE TO AGREE TO THIS POLICY. **

**YOU AFFIRM THAT YOU ARE EITHER MORE THAN 18 YEARS OF AGE( 19 Maine), OR AN EMANCIPATED MINOR, OR POSSESS LEGAL PARENTAL OR GUARDIAN CONSENT, AND ARE FULLY ABLE AND COMPETENT TO ENTER INTO THE TERMS, CONDITIONS, OBLIGATIONS, AFFIRMATIONS, REPRESENTATIONS, AND WARRANTIES SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND TO ABIDE BY AND COMPLY WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IN ANY CASE, YOU AFFIRM THAT YOU ARE OVER THE AGE OF 13, AS THE SITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE** **, YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO USE OR EVEN ACCESS THE SITE AND/OR THE SERVICES OR TO CREATE AN ACCOUNT.**

Further **,** if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or any of its terms, please do not provide us with your personally identifiable information (“PII”), for example any personal information capable of being associated with you individually through one or more identifiers. 

Our business changes constantly, and our T&Cs, any rules posted on the Site, as well as this Privacy Policy may change too. You should check the Site frequently to see if there are recent changes. EZWin reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of this Site or any of the Services (as hereinafter defined), shall be deemed an irrevocable acceptance of any such revisions. 

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you.The above sentence notwithstanding, this Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by EZWin. 

**IMPORTANT INFORMATION TO NOTE:**

  * **PLEASE BE AWARE THAT ANY PII THAT YOU SUBMIT AS PART OF YOUR ENTERANCE INTO OR SUBMISSION TO A SWEEPSTAKES, CONTEST, GAME OR OTHER PROMOTION (HEREINAFTER “PROMOTION”) MAY BE USED AND DISPLAYED PUBLICLY. YOUR APPROVAL OF THIS PROVISION AND THE ABILITY TO SHARE YOUR PII PUBLICLY IS AN INTEGRAL PART OF ANY PROMOTION. IF YOU DO NOT WANT YOUR PII SHARED PUBLICLY, DO NOT ENTER ANY PROMOTION ON THE SITE.**

  * If you cancel your membership and decide that you want to remove your personal information from this Site, you must contact us at _[info@ezwingame.com](mailto:info@ezwingame.com)_ and request that such information be removed. However, please be advised that it may be impossible to permanently remove your information from our backup system or from the Internet as the information may continue to exist in cached pages, etc. 

  * In order to have access to some of the Services provided on this Site or through our mobile services, you will have to register with the Site and create a login and password. 

  * **BY CREATING AN ACCOUNT AT THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO RECEIVE FREE CONTENT AND/OR PROMOTIONAL OFFERS FROM US AS WELL AS ANY THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS.**

  * Upon submission of your PII to this Site, you are agreeing to the T&Cs of this Site, its rules, including any rules governing our Promotions, and this Privacy Policy. As long as you use, create an account, access our mobile or online services or participate in any Promotion you agree to be bound by the T&Cs, rules and this Privacy Policy. 

  1. **Description of the Site.** EZWin and the Site allow registered users ("Players") to play Games for Prizes are based on free sweepstakes with members having free particpation for each Game. The Site shall, now or in the future, integrate the ability of Players to play, engage and interact online and on mobile devices (the "Services"). The term Service(s) shall include all Services including Online and Mobile Services as well as Sweepstakes, Games, Contests, user interaction, content Submissions and all any other promotional activities.

Each Service may be governed by its own rules (the “Rules”) as this Privacy Policy. In the event that any term, condition, clause or provision of this Privacy Policy conflicts with any term, condition, clause or provision contained in the Rules, the term, condition, clause, or provision of this Privacy Policy shall be controlling. In order to post or submit any videos, audio, pictures, documents, texts, comments, profiles, Mobile/SMS or other submissions (“Submissions”), visitors or users may be required to become Members (as hereinafter defined) by registering with the Site and creating a login and password. 

  2. **What information does the Site collect?**

**Non-member Activity.** Visitors to the Site may choose to browse, search and examine Submissions and the Site without registering with the Site and becoming a Member. Visitors to the Site may also undertake any such actions that are permitted of non-members in accordance with the Rules of any Service. When you visit our Site as a non-Member, we collect only information you provide or submit to the Site directly, information you send to us by email, information and messages you send or post through our accounts on third party social networks (such as Facebook, YouTube or Twitter) or information or messages you send through our SMS or mobile services. The foregoing statement not withstanding, our servers may recognize and collect visitors’ domain names, IP addresses and any information on pages visited. 

**Member Activity.** In order to have access to some of the Services, mentioned above, including entering Sweepstakes, playing Games or providing other Submissions, a user or visitor must be a registered Member of the Site. We may ask for and collect some PII when you create an account, including, but not limited to your e-mail address, name and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. We may also collect such PII as you hometown, age, gender, street address and telephone number. Once you become a member, we also collect a variety of information and PII depending on the Services you use or engage in.

We may collect additional PII as part of a survey, including biographical, marital, educational and career information. We may also collect information you submit outside of the Site but as part of a Promotion. For example, we may collect information on Sweepstakes entries or guesses you submit as part of the Mobile Services we provide. 

**Content Uploaded to the Site.** Any PII or Submissions that you voluntarily disclose online (for example, PII contained in your comments, messages, or profile pages, if any) becomes publicly available and can be collected, viewed and used by third parties. **Usage Information.** We may collect information about your usage, such as when you use the Site, the Submissions you make, the Games you play, the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in the Site. If you are logged in we may associate this information with your account. 

  3. **How do we use the information you provide us?** We use your PII such as your name, address, and e-mail address in order to provide you with the Services. All information that you submit to us is governed by this Privacy Policy, the T&Cs and any other Rules. 

    * We may share your PII with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, mobile services billings, e-mail origination, support services, customer relationship management services, order fulfillment, and contests, sweepstakes and/ or promotional fulfillment. 

    * We may also use such PII to determine if you comply with any of the Rules provided for on this Site.

    * Your account name (not your e-mail address) you create during registration may be displayed to other users/visitors/Members when you provide Submissions such as submitting Sweepstakes or Game entries or commenting and other Members can contact you through comments, blogs, chat, or forums. Any Submission that you provide through the Site may be redistributed through the Internet to other websites and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

    * **UNLESS YOU OPT-OUT, WE MAY USE YOUR E-MAIL OR OTHER PII TO SEND COMMERCIAL OR MARKETING MESSAGES WITHOUT YOUR FURTHER CONSENT. FURTHER UNLESS YOU OPT-OUT, WE MAY SELL, TRANSFER OR OTHERWISE PROVIDE YOUR PII TO THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS FOR COMMERCIAL OR MARKETING PURPOSES WITHOUT YOUR FURTHER CONSENT.**

    * Be advised that we use your e-mail address and other contact information provided by you to contact you regarding your Sweepstakes and Game Submissions. We may also use your e-mail address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or customer service purposes). 

    * You may opt-out at any time by changing your preferences. Your preferences can be changed by sending a request to _[info@ezwingame.com](mailto:info@ezwingame.com)_ or following the instructions provided on the Site.

    * We use both your PII and certain non-PII (such as anonymous user data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality and services by storing, tracking, analyzing and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications. 

  4. **Information that is Publicly Available.**

    * When you create an account and become a Member of the Site, some information about your account and/or your account activity may be provided to other users/visitors of the Site. This information may include, but is not limited to, username and any sweepstakes or other Promotion entry made.

    * Please be aware that any information that you submit as part of your Sweepstakes, Game or Promotion entry may be used and displayed publicly in the event that you win a Prize. If you do not want your PII shared publicly, do not register with the Site or enter any Sweepstakes, Game or other Promotion. 

    * Any Submission that you provide through the Site may be redistributed through the Internet and/or other media channels and may be viewed by the general public. 

  * **Third Party Advertisers & Third Party Links. ****BY CREATING AN ACCOUNT AT THE SITE, YOU CONSENT TO RECEIVE FREE CONTENT AND/OR PROMOTIONAL OFFERS FROM US OR ANY THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS.** You may withdraw your consent at anytime by changing your account preferences or contacting us at info@ezwingame.com. 

If any financial information is collected it will be used to bill the Member/user for services offered on the Site or our Mobile Services. If you used a credit card or a mobile phone account to pay for any fee on the Site or engage in any paid Service, your credit card or mobile phone account information may be subject to verification by the issuing credit card company or other third party company. Unless you give us permission at the time such information is collected, this information will not be used for any purpose except for the fulfillment and record keeping of the transaction.

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link to, and/or frame within the Site. We also may participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors and Members and/or users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. We encourage you to read the policies of these third party websites. By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or sponsored by third parties or advertisers through third party links on the Site, or electing to receive communications (such as e-mails) or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes or other programs, offered or sponsored by third parties on the Site, you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties.Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party websites (even if offered on or through our Site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for the independent policies or actions of third parties, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Services and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback on not only the Services, but for sites we link to as well. 

Further, any linking with any other web site is neither an endorsement of that site nor any of the products or services that may be offered on that site. 

**Note:** Your PII or financial information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets of EZWin or a bankruptcy. We may also disclose PII or financial information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of EZWin or other visitors to the Site. Whenever PII or financial information is disclosed under this paragraph, we may also disclose your demographic information on a non-anonymous basis. 

  5. **How does EZWin Protect Users Personal Information?** We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your PII on our systems. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Third parties may unlawfully attempt to intercept or access transmissions or private communications and other Members and/or visitors may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

  6. **Does EZWin Use Cookies?** We use cookies for our own advertising purposes. We may use third-party advertising technology to serve ads when you visit the Site and sites upon which we advertise. This technology uses information about your visits to the Site and the sites upon which we advertise, (not including your name, address, or other personal information), to serve our ads to you. In the course of serving our advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we may use web beacons, provided by our ad serving partner, to help manage our online advertising. These web beacons enable our ad server to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site and to learn which banner ads bring users to our Site. 

  7. **How do you change PII provided or OPT-OUT?** EZWin gives Members an option for modifying or removing their information from our database. To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for you account, contact us at _[info@ezwingame.com](mailto:info@ezwingame.com)_. We will comply with your requests as reasonably as we can. Please note that we require some PII for billing purposes. If you wish to delete your name, e-mail address or mailing address you may be required to terminate your account. However, please note, that while you may remove your PII from the site at any time, you acknowledge that we may retain archived or cached copies of your PII. Please submit any questions and requests regarding your PII submitted as part of an application to _[info@ezwingame.com](mailto:info@ezwingame.com)_

  8. **Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

**Widgets**

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

**Import Contacts**

You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.

**Facebook Connect**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect . These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

  8. By visiting the Site and/or using the Service, including, but not limited to making Sweepstakes or Game entries, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes within this page so our visitors/users/Members are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

  9. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.Any material change in the Company's privacy practices will be posted on the web site under the privacy policy and the home page. Before any material changes will be implemented this change will be prominently on the home page posted on the Web site 30 calendar days prior to implementing the change.

Be sure to review our Privacy Policy, T&Cs and any Rules regularly so that you will be aware of any changes to them. Please remember that your continued use of this Site, participation in any Sweepstakes, Game or other Promotion, utilization of our Mobile Services and/or maintenance of an account after changes or revisions have been made constitute your acceptance of such updates. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy of the Site, please contact us at:

EZWin Game LLC

6400 N. Andrews Avenue, Suite #320

Ft. Lauderdale, FL 33309
